Hello Hello Friends Welcome to Voice
Secondary School We are going to talk about the
stock of SBI Cards Many people will be
talking about it especially
about Bewakoof because it has
reached near its breakfast again and the
best thing is that we will also look at it in the stock
and try to understand how the question is being formed
but this question is what is the
opportunity to print money,
you will see the statement that came out, if you read this what is the opportunity to
print money or what is the opportunity that the
meaning of things changes above the comma then we will
try to understand it peacefully and
before moving forward let me tell you that you should
subscribe to the channel on subscribe quickly
press the bell icon so that your
notification is left halfway
and to learn fashion you should join
click on the membership join button and along with that
practice is very important
risk management is more important than that keep
practicing and keep learning keep
teaching we will take you straight to
SBI Cards market capitalization of one lakh crore, it is the
only stock
in its segment which is listed, rest of the
cards, credit card related things
No one is listed, in the coming time we hope that
even a gypsy's card comes forward and gets
listed but at present there
is only one player listed in SBI card, friend cigarette
profit. If we talk about tremendous profit, there is
no shortage. Because of this very reason, it is trading at such a high
speed that it is trading on IPL.
Tremendous profitability,
tremendous I would say maintained growth. Look, not only
this, you can see how the
front's profit was in 2014.
Look at today's date, this statement is showing the profitability of 12 crore servants and Ravana worth thousand crores.
If you see
how the revenue is being generated,
9000 crore Jairam profit, see Chittor
thousand crore, one and a half, 9058 profitability,
see 12 crore, you got it, then there is a very
good profitability. We will not limit ourselves to this, we will
understand further as well. Before that, let's
not leave any stone unturned. Now, the industry
by carb lines, there was a blast, it has reached directly from 1190,
13 forts are being built. The
video comes for you in advance first, Army
Channel  The monthly pullback and it definitely took some time to see
where the explosion has reached and
watch this video, Kotak Mahindra Bank was satisfied
just by standing on the strength of level 2000,
then to understand the process, see, in one or two
months, it wreaked havoc and in tow,
especially Tata Motors, you got
to see a big rally, we did not stop here, you will
understand this topic which we are talking about,
SBI Cards, SBI Cards
monthly chart, some
McKay function, see this, big channels
with big volume, but now I will look at this along with the small
time Brijbalala time, Prince Harry's minister,
now let us understand the weekly
time print which cannot cause cancer
and will also see the positive effect,
big rally, correction, big rally
again and again, reaction
123 again, the same three times, again the same
demand,
increasing, increasing, increasing, you
see the volume, you are done, this is
looking like a dangerous situation, I mean, you have
seen how
profit booking was seen in these areas, or not,
if you will look at it for some time, then
Large block deals have taken place here,
and whether it's a bulk deal or a block link, they're
better exchanged hands this way
between very big players. Well,
what kind of situation is this? We'll type in small print and
try to understand it. Then,
if we understand in detail,
how big is the sentence? DL Meena was cut. You
see, the price was solid. We have
Rahu above it. Before that,
you got loose. And still, see what to
put in. So, these beans, where big people took
out the goods here and exchanged,
hands were exchanged here in the same way.
Now you will see this, I have brought a video for you.
But there is a
positivity in breakfast, whenever it happens,
you should see the situation in this way. In this way, I
mean, that area is being repeatedly visited
and along with this, in the order in this way.
When will this area break? When you
look here, you will see consolidation near it with
very low volume, which
I am seeing right now, and
a large volume candle which will be formed in this way, it  It
can have the courage to cross it in the
coming time, so that's why
1234 is stupid and has reached the same level again,
so the coming time is very important,
pro, after half an hour,
see, once after reduction and relation, it has
reached the same level again, a positive
attitude is a good thing, the
demand is this low point, you will see
that the low point is gradually reaching, it seems that
orders are
gradually coming down in these areas and a demand zone is
increasing, you got a
high quality thing, so I will
try to tell you from both the tests, now this
consolidation is that, Polytechnic
information is always your friend,
explain it, now it will not end here, now it will be
very important in the coming few weeks, now
whenever I talk about breakfast, it is
understood in two ways, so
generally if you go by the level of breakfast, then
consolidation correction is a
good thing, but the best thing is that
I
think an even better situation than that, see if any stock  It's
reaching breakfast levels. Look, this way, the
curry leaves are being removed, the demand is
going down, and after that, there's a
pullback after breaking out. So, when
you're not secure, there's a
pullback after black. Where there's no T-shirt, then a
pullback situation is better.
Understand this. If it's not charity, will there be a
pullback? So, that's why
I'm bringing you a video. See, if it's
not charity, it seems like there's a
lot of breakups, then the chances of Jaya, which if you do
n't understand the record properly, sometimes it happens there, then
fighting comes down completely.
Suppose it went up to here, then the
situation became like this again, and then it came down to, lo, hello,
one. So, the value is
definitely tremendous, but
what confidence will come for the pullback? It's a pullback, so understand this. I'll
keep a lot of people at home, who prefer
slippers over breakouts. There was a pullback with a lower value
breakfast. Okay, when the pullback came, you must have
seen it, so your volume will increase when the
pullback comes. Income Burger.  This volume will be
your job, so this is a very good way to
identify the north-east direction and pullback. Let me
ask you a question myself,
what do you like here,
tell me based on your own experience.
If you ask me, then
in a better situation, if I have any
tax, in breakfast, we have our
simple slide in between, so we have to
look at small time platforms correction.
If we look at the total validity of pullback, what are they?
Exactly the
starting of the next pimples, but there is a lot of understanding part, that
here we have very less
breakfast, I have already removed a big one, so
one risk factor is
full, that is why I
personally like pullback because
we do not get a low response.
To increase confidence, the volume of pullback is very less,
so it is a better situation, there is
more conviction and I have
more confidence, so in this way, in
this way you can gradually improve
your situation.  By experience, you will
understand the things of the break after folder. Now I have
seen an example of this type from TCS.
Look, this
area was getting hit repeatedly. I was watching the spot in the same
way. Demand gradually increased. And
finally, what happened to breakfast? What is
happening to you? It is a good pull, then there is another
good wine and a good pull back,
but it seems the volume has increased. Understand, which
I will do. Then you will
see it here after some time. How will you see the situation, that you have
seen the SBI card, understood?
But if you look at it in a little more detail,
RSL, please forgive me,
Superman,
this point
here, I
mean, I am
Superman here. If here, as
I said, there was consolidation in the last two weeks,
and consolidation is a very good friend,
what about your consolidation is very important. So, in the
coming time, if there is another
record, then you will see this level also
increasing. And because of the last two times, all
this is more in our Dal Maya super momentum.  It is
giving conditions, that is why our
festivals are very important even before this, that is why I am very
important, but this stuffed many people were
not taken back in the chapter of credit, then
tried to go back, again
considering, but this time it is once, rather keep the
consolidation of focus from last Dubai,
but I would say let the confirmation come
here a little and for Brett, if you are playing then
keep the person a little tight here so that like last time, if things
trail, then you get the exact knickers, there is
no time and you are not able to mess with the room, if
you liked this video and Vikram video,
please do like it, the
price is a few coins,
keep practicing and along with this,
I would say this about risk management, do
our small work also, make people grand,
how important is your past in family circle and friend circle and you have to
work hard for it, thank you, thank you for watching
my video